Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Publications, 1974-1987, Series 6:; (Boxes 13-15; 2.75 linear feet)
  - Journal, 1981-1987, 6.2
    - Issue #31 (Box 13)
      - "Trends, Traditions, and Dirt: an Opinionated Guide to the Current State of Art in Northern California" by Robert Atkins, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - "Exhibitions in Print," 1981 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Issue #32 (Box 13)
      - Editorial Materials, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 33)
      - "[introduction]" by Frances Colpitt, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 34)
      - "The Importance of Permanence" by Donald Judd, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 35)
      - "Intentional Acts of Identification: Legrady and Maclay" by Mark Johnstone, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 36)
      - "Mr. Smith Goes to the Airport" by Michael Smith, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 37)
      - "Bruce Nauman Interview" by Robert Smith, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 38)
      - "Magnificent Obsession: the Drawings of David Smith" by Sally Ruth Bourrie, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 39)
      - "Anthony Caro's Emma Lake Sculptures" by Phyllis Tuchman, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 40)
      - "The Activity Art of Allan Kaprow and the Notion of Functional Sculpture" by Dan Giesler, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 41)
      - "Context: Light and Space as Art" by Jan Butterfield, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 42)
      - "Artist Pages," 1982 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Issue #33 (Box 13)
      - Editorial Materials 1982 (Box 13, Folder 44)
      - "[introduction]" by Richard Hertz, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 45)
      - "Art Norms in 1982" by Ted Castle, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 46)
      - "Art Fashion" by David Carrier, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 47)
      - "Popular Imagery" by Jeremy Gilbert-Rolfe, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 48)
      - "The Difference Between Absence and Not Being Missed" by Geralyn Donohue and Joan Wallace, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 49)
      - "Too Good to Be True" by Thomas Lawson, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 50)
      - "Paragraphs Towards an Essay Entitled 'Restoration Comedies'" by Howard Singerman, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 51)
      - "Movies as Modern Muse" by Gerard Haggerty, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 52)
      - "A Brief Commentary on Latin American Art" by Imogen Sieveking, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 53)
      - "Photography: a Bourgeois Success Story" by James Hugunin, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 54)
      - "Words and Pictures" by John Brumfield, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 55)
      - Unused Manuscripts, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Issue #34 (Box 13)
      - Editorial Materials, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 57)
      - "On Pictures and Meanings" by John Brumfield, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 58)
      - "On Number, Time, and Emotion" by John Whitney, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 59)
      - "Defining the Avant Garde" by Richard Hertz, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 60)
      - "Art With a Capital 'A' and Television Executives" by Michael Delgado, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 61)
      - "The Art Economist" by Ken Friedman, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 62)
      - "The Open Road of Risk: George Herms, Wallace Berman, the Beats and West Coast Visionary Poetics" by Robert L. Pincus, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 63)
      - "The Figurative Style of the Early Sixties: Brice, Lebrun, Warshaw" by Michael Kohn, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 64)
      - "The Psychobiological Imperative" by Marilyn Ekdahl Ravicz, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 65)
      - "Artist Pages," 1982 (Box 13, Folder 66)
      - Unused Manuscripts, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 67)
      - Unused Photographs, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Issue #35 (Box 13)
      - Editorial Materials, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 69)
      - "History Repeats Itself (Part One)," 1983 (Box 13, Folder 70)
      - "The Artist and Television" by Kathy Huffman, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 71)
      - "Art in search of a Public" by Susan Boettger, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 72)
      - "Interview: Henry Gajewski" by Judith Hoffberg, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - Issue #36 (Box 14)
      - Editorial Materials, 1982-1983, (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
      - "The Garret, the Boardroom and the Amusement Park" by John Chase, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - "Golden Architecture" by Alan Hess, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - "Micromodels: Drawings of Five Works of Architecture" by Robert Mangurian, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - "Five Basic Classifications of Building Production" by Elizabeth McMillian, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - "L.A. Preserving the Commonplace" by David Gebhard, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - "David Ireland's House" by Robert Atkins, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - "Robert Wilhite" by John Bowsher, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - "Scott Burton" by Ronny Cohen, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - "R.M. Fisher" by John Perreault, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - "This Furniture is Not to Be Sat On Or Sit on My Sculpture" by Frances Colpitt, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - "Jim Iserman" by Melinda Wortz, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Unused Manuscripts, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Issue #37 (Box 14)
      - Editorial Materials, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - "History Repeats Itself (Part Two)," 1983, (4 folders) (Box 14, Folder 16-19)
      - "Why I Go To the Movies Alone" by Richard Prince, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - "Representational Drawing Today" by Phyllis Plous, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - "After the Revolution: Cuba in Photographs" by Emily Hicks, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - "Big Folks" by Susan Muchnic, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - "Is it Curtains For the T.V. Window?" by Beverly O'Neill, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - "The Rocket Ship Tree" by John Beach, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - "Gordon Wagner: Magician and Mythmaker" by Judith Hoffberg, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Issue #38 (Box 14)
      - Editorial Materials, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - "Architecture on Film: Mallet-Stevens to Meerson" by Donald Albrecht, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - "Confrontational Icons" by Robert Pincus, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - "Future Video: Max Almy" by Louise Lewis, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - "TV's Past Exposed" by Beverly O'Neill, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Issue #39 (Box 14)
      - Editorial Materials, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - "Portrait, in Eclipse" by Jeff Perrone, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - "The Treatise of Narcissus" by Andre Gide, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - "Home" by Hal Foster, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 35)
      - "Ajax" by Mike Kelley, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 36)
      - "Picasso" by Gertrude Stein, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 37)
      - "Mrs. Battle s Opinions on Whist" by Charles Lamb, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 38)
      - "The Deceitful Artist" by Giacomo Casanova, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Issue #40 (Box 14)
      - Editorial Materials, 1984, (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 40-41)
      - "[introduction]", 1984 (Box 14, Folder 42)
      - "The Hydrogen Jukebox: Terror, Narcissism, and Art" by Peter Schjeldahl, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 43)
      - "Crepe de Chine" by Kim MacConnel, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 44)
      - "A New Found Career" by Martha Rosler, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 45)
      - "Images That Understand Us: a Conversation With David Salle and James Welling," 1984 (Box 14, Folder 46)
      - "The Poltergeist" by David Askevold and Mike Kelley, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 47)
      - "Art Into Play" by Jean Fisher, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 48)
      - "What is to Be Learned?" by Peter Plagens, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 49)
      - "Interviews" by Robert Pincus, 1984, (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 50-51)
      - "Introduction" by Daniel Alexander Wasil, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 52)
      - "Turning the Conversation" by Kim Gordon, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 53)
      - "On John Knight's Journals Work" by Dan Graham, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 54)
      - "The Deceitful Artist" by Giacomo Casanova, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Issue #41 (Box 14)
      - Editorial Materials, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 55-56)
      - "Iceland: Gateway to Hell" by Jeffrey Vallance, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 57)
      - "Factory Sets From 'Cinderella'" by Ericka Beckman, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 58)
      - "Expressionism" by Benjamin Weissman, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 59)
      - "Jenny Bolande," 1985 (Box 14, Folder 60)
      - "Simon Weasel" by Paul McMahon and Nancy Chun, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 61)
      - "The Commodity as Country Music Theme" by John Miller, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 62)
      - "To Marie Osmond" by Jack Skelley, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 63)
      - "Scores For 'Parallel,' 'Chinks/Weathervane,' and 'Coat Dance'" by Brina Gehry, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 64)
      - "Hand in Glove" by Dennis Cooper, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 65)
      - "The Death of a Guerrilla Poet" by Dan Walworth, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 66)
      - "A Conversation with Lynne Tillman and Sheila McLaughlin" by Stephen Prina and Christopher Williams, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 67)
      - "Living With Bad Faith" by Kathi Norklun, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 68)
      - "Demenstruation" by Mitchell Syrop, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Issue #42 (Box 14)
      - Editorial Materials, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 70-71)
      - "Plato's Cave, Rothko's Chapel, Lincoln's Profile" by Mike Kelley, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 72)
      - "To a Swan" by David Shapiro, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 73)
      - "Multiplicity, Proliferation, Reconvention" by Jeremy Gilbert-Rolfe, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 74)
      - "On Line" by Peter Halley, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 75)
      - "Idea as Multiplicity" by Gilles Deleuze, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 76)
      - "Stereoscope and Kaleidoscope" by Jonathan Crary, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 77)
      - "Thomas Nozkowski: Painting and Proliferation" by Joseph Masheck, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 78)
      - "Je/Autre" by Gary Parent, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 79)
      - "Nature" by Kimball Lockhart, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 80)
      - "Some Notes on Proliferation, Process, History" by Sande Cohen, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 81)
      - "Falsework" by Gregory Rukavina, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 82)
      - "Mass, Crowd and Pack" by Michel Feher, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 83)
      - "The Bubble-Child" by Jean Baudrillard, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - "America's Borders Are Everywhere" by Alan Sekula, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - "The Ditmarsh Tale of Lies" by the Brothers Grimm, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - "The Procession of Udine" by T.S. Martin, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - "Spitting Out an Eyeful at the Film Feast" by Ellen Kaufman, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Issue #43 (Box 15)
      - Editorial Materials, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 6-7)
      - "If You Die in the University Hospital" by Michael Lesy, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - "An Editorial" by Connie Fitzsimmons, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - "The Invention of the World" by Jochen Gerz, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - "On Criticism" by Ron Linden, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - "From Minds Meet" by Walter Abish, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - "Glitches" by Marina La Palma, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - "Shoot Out in Boulder" by William Burroughs, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - "Encounter..." by Marc Schepers, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - "A Clever Ad" by Robert Morgan, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - "I Have No Face" by Johanna Drucker, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - "Hansel and Gretel" by Louis Hock and Elizabeth Sisco, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - "VAMP R Y" by Judith Barry, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - "Diseuse" by Theresa Hak Kyung Cha, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - "Seduced By Analogy" by Bob Perelman, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - "The Ricky Paul Show" by Eric Bogosian, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - "Anniversaries of Defeat" by Gregory Lukow, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - "All Flesh is Grass" by Amy Gerstler, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Unused Manuscripts, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Issue #44 (Box 15)
      - Editorial Materials, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - "Tiny Alice" by Nancy Evans, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - "David Cabrera," 1986 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - Unused Manuscripts, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Issue #45 (Box 15)
      - Editorial Materials, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 30-31)
      - Manuscript, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Issue #46 (Box 15)
      - Editorial Materials, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 33)
      - "Fear of Success" by Tim Power, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      - "TV Generations" by Judy Fiskin, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 35)
      - "Learning About Great Art" by Ilene Segalove, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 36)
      - "[editor's note]" by Marcos Sanchez-Tranqulino, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 37)
      - "The Chicano/a Artist Inside and Outside the Mainstream" by Harry Gamboa, Jr., 1987 (Box 15, Folder 38)
      - "Should Art Historians Know Their Place?" by John Tagg, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 39)
      - "Mano a Mano: an Essay On the Representation of the Zoot Suit and Its Misrepresentation by Octavio Paz" by Marcos Sanchez-Tranquilino, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 40)
      - "Art in Public Places" by Al Nodal, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 41)
      - "Untitled" by Jamey Bair, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 42)
      - Unused Manuscripts, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Issue #48 (Box 15)
      - Editorial Materials, 1987, (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 44-45)
      - Manuscript, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 46)
      - [cover], 1987 (Box 15, Folder 47)
      - "Local/International," 1987 (Box 15, Folder 48)
      - "Chicago Artists," 1987 (Box 15, Folder 49)
      - "London Artists," 1987 (Box 15, Folder 50)
      - "Los Angeles Artists," 1987 (Box 15, Folder 51)
      - "Eight Artists Respond to a Photo," 1987 (Box 15, Folder 52)
      - "New York Artists," 1987 (Box 15, Folder 53)
      - "Pirri Mantegna Petroiusti Roma," 1987 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Issue #49 (Box 15)
      - Editorial Materials 1987 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Unknown Issue (Box 15)
      - Manuscripts and Photographs, circa late 1980s (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Printed Materials, 1974-1986, 6.3
    This subseries consists of four issues of LAICA's Journal (#14, April, 1977; #18, April, 1978; #25, December, 1979; #29, Summer, 1981). Also found here is a complete set (1974-1986) of LAICA's in-house newsletter. Early newsletters contain minutes and transcripts of committee meetings. In addition to LAICA's calendar, some newsletters contain a citywide calendar for art events. A 1977-1978 copy of the Artist Calendar provides an exhibition schedule for Los Angeles galleries.
    - Artist's Calendar, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Journal #14, April-May 1977 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Journal #18, April-May 1978 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Journal #25, November-December 1979 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Journal #29, Summer 1981 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Newsletter #1-17, April 1974-January 1976 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Newsletter #18-35, February 1976-November 1977 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Newsletter #36-48, December 1977-December 1978 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Newsletter #49-60, January 1979-December 1979 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Newsletter #61-71, January 1980-December 1980 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Newsletter #72-90, January 1981-November/December 1982 (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Newsletter #91-108, January/February 1983-March/April 1986 (Box 15, Folder 68)
- Photographs, mid 1970s-1983, Series 7:; (Box 15; 11 folders)
  General photographs of LAICA facilities, staff, events, and meetings are filed here. There are photographs of LAICA's buildings on Robertson Boulevard and Traction Avenue. Staff members photographed include Robert and Tobi Smith, Debra Burchett-Lere, Michael Delgado, and Bridget Johnson. Also included are photographs of an Advocates meeting attended by Los Angeles City Councilman Joel Wachs, and a visit to LAICA by Joan Mondale.
  Additional photographs are filed in the Exhibitions and Programs series. Slides are filed in Series 8, Slides.
  - Accessibility Documentation, circa 1979 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Advocates Annual Meeting, June 1983 (Box 15, Folder 70)
    Attended by Los Angeles City Councilman Joel Wachs
  - Buildings, mid 1970s-early 1980s (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Contact Sheets, circa 1970s (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Events, circa 1970s (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Meetings, circa 1970s (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Negatives, circa 1970s (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Offices, circa 1970s, (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 76-77)
  - Staff, circa 1970s (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Visit by Joan Mondale, March 1979 (Box 15, Folder 80)
- Slides, 1974-1987, Series 8:; (Boxes 16-18; 3 linear feet)
  All slides in the collection are filed in this series for preservation housing. The bulk of slides were separated from the Exhibitions and Programs series and provide comprehensive documentation of exhibitions, works of art, and events. Additional slides document LAICA's facilities, staff events and a staff party, the CETA-funded Artist-in-Residence program, and works of art from the Artist Files. Slides are arranged by broad program area, exhibition, or artist name and chronologically within each grouping.
  - LAICA: Century City Location, circa 1974-1977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - LAICA: 2020 South Robertson Boulevard Location, circa 1977 (Box 16)
  - LAICA: 811 Traction Avenue Location, circa 1980 (Box 16)
  - LAICA: Exhibition Committee Meeting, circa late 1970s-early 1980s (Box 16)
  - LAICA: Handicap Accessibility, circa 1980 (Box 16)
  - LAICA: Offices, circa 1977-mid 1980s (Box 16)
  - LAICA: Offices, circa 1977-mid 1980s (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - LAICA: Promotional Materials, circa 1974-1980 (Box 16)
  - LAICA: Staff Party, circa 1977-mid 1980s (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Exhibitions, January 1975-January 1976 (Box 16)
  - Exhibitions, March 1976-March 1977 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Exhibitions, October 1977-December 1977 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Exhibitions, January 1978-June 1978 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Exhibitions, September 1978-October 1978 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Exhibitions, November 1978-February 1979 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Exhibitions, February 1979-May 1979 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Exhibitions, June 1979 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Exhibitions, June 1979-July 1979 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Exhibitions, August 1979-October 1979 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Exhibitions, November 1979-March 1980 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Exhibitions, April 1980-May 1980 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Exhibitions, May 1980-June 1980 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Exhibitions, June 1980-July 1980 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Exhibitions, August 1980-September 1980 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Exhibitions, September 1980 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Exhibitions, September 1980-December 1980 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Exhibitions, January 1981-March 1981 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Exhibitions, March 1981-September 1981 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Exhibitions, October 1981-November 1981 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Exhibitions, November 1981-January 1982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Exhibitions, February 1982-October 1982 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Exhibitions, October 1982-March 1983 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Exhibitions, April 1983-November 1983 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Exhibitions, January 1984 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Exhibitions, March 1984 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Exhibitions, March 1984-July 1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Exhibitions, July 1984 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Exhibitions, October 1984 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Exhibitions, December 1984-April 1985 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Exhibitions, April 1985-June 1985 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Exhibitions, June 1985-October 1985 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Exhibitions, January 1986- February 1987 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Proposed Exhibits, "A-Au" (Box 17)
  - Proposed Exhibits, "Bu-De" (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Proposed Exhibits, "Eu-Ta" (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Unknown Exhibitions, circa 1974-1985 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Events, December 1978-November 1979 (Box 18)
  - Events, May 1980-March 1983 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Larry Albright, circa 1978 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Peter Alexander, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Ed Cabajal, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Vija Celmins, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Anthony Hernandez, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Bob Gibson, circa 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Pat Hogan, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Mark Kaiserman, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Maria Kwong, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Leslie Labowitz-Straus, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Carole Langston, circa 1979-1980 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Jilly Lauren, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Peter Lodato, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: John Miller, circa 1978 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Tommy Nation, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Jeff Perkins, circa 1978-1980 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Vaughan Rachel, circa 1979-1980 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Jane Reynolds, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Allen Ruppersberg, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Doni Silver, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Judy Simonian, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Jean Thrift, circa 1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Bob Wilhite, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA Artists in Residence: Richard Yokomi, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA: Victoria Blythe Lecture on Paper Conservation, circa 1979 (Box 18)
  - CETA Day, June 1978 (Box 18)
  - CPR Training Session, circa 1979 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - CETA: Anthony Hernandez Lecture on Current Photography, circa 1978 (Box 18)
  - CETA: How to Make a Stretcher Bar, circa 1978-1980 (Box 18)
  - CETA: Peter Lodato Lecture, January 1979 (Box 18)
  - CETA: Richard Newton Lecture on Art in Public Places, August 1979 (Box 18)
  - CETA: Performance Workshop, circa 1979 (Box 18)
  - CETA: Plaza de la Raza, circa 1978-1980 (Box 18)
  - CETA: Project Documentation, circa 1978-1980 (Box 18)
  - CETA: Songwriters Resources Workshop, circa 1978-1980 (Box 18)
  - CETA: John White Performance and Lecture, June 1979 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Artist Files: Dieter Appelt (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Alvaro Asturais (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: John Baldessari (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Marilyn Baum (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Cliff Benjamin (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: John Berens (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: [?] Blaine (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Nayland Blake (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Genevive Blons (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Marie Brumund (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Ned Cartledge (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Eileen Cowin (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Dave Cunningham (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: [Deeton?] (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Raul De Soto (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Guy Dill (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Maria Downey (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Barbara Drucker (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Bruce Edelstein (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Linda Ekstrom (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Shiela Elias (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Merion Estes (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Macduff Everton (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Paul Gervais (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Artist Files: Jean Glassman (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Mike Glier (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: [?] Green (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: [?] Hagman (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Keith Haring (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Christopher Charles Hill (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Nancy Holt (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Jenny Holzer (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: E'Wao Kagoshima (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Eve Laramee (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Peter Levinson (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Francine Matarazzo (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Michael McMillen (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Jeff Millikan (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Anna Valentina Morch (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Selma Moskowitz (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Alfredo Nunez (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Richard Parker (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Peter Plagens (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Steve Prina (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Carol Quint (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Charles Ray (Box 18)
  - Artist Files: Ed Ruscha (Box 18)